I'm gonna get in an argument with you.
What the hell?
I'm behind the scenes, but they're adding one thing at a time, and I'm out front.
Oh, you're gonna be in the front?
I'm just trying to hang in there.
I'm really enjoying being a Dorking type.
I thought it was too soon.
what am i gonna do?
I don't know what to do
Let's get on with today's activities, and I'd like to present you with this project.
Short Project Presentation Contest
What I mean by this is, there are short videos on YouTube, right?
Yes, there are.
That's right. We can use these short videos to attract new fans,
We are planning to use these short videos to attract new fans and to increase the visibility of Rough Rough Rough,
We asked everyone to come up with a short video project in advance.
And now we are going to ask you to present them.
And if it can be shot here, we'll shoot it now.
I see.
And then we will upload the pictures we have taken,
I was given some advice from Mr. Sakuma about what I should do, and I decided to do it.
Let's hear it now.
Who would like to start? Let's start with me.
Let's start with me. Okay. Then, Natsume.
Okay.
The short project I came up with is,
It's a heart-throbbing joke Shiritori.
Oh...
What's this "heart-throbbing line Shiritori"?
Well, it's just what it sounds like,
I'm going to make a Shiritori (a short game of Shiritori) with cute and cute lines, and play it among the members.
Oh, so you mean you're going to connect them?
Oh, yes, to connect them.
If it started with "Um, Natsume started...", then it would be one person per video?
Does that mean one person per video?
No, it's not like that,
If I say something like, "Oh, it's a raw egg," you know?
Then the next member would connect it with "ne, ne.
You mean raw eggs?
Ruff Ruff's heart throbbing jellyfish fritillary
You have a cute face like an apple!
I can't sleep, so sleep with me.
And, oh, I caught a bowl of rice!
When did you buy these eggs?
Yes, it's over. It's over. What is it, Mr. Saito? You're being pulled by the raw egg you just bought.
What did you say?
When did you buy the eggs?
Victory.
I think this is something that could be improved, Mr. Sakuma.
I don't know if I want to be a heartthrob, but I'm aiming for something really interesting.
What do you mean? A fun word-shiritori game with a heart-crushing effect?
Funny word shiritori
Let's try this.
I don't like idols who say lines like this.
Let's try Shiritori.
Okay, let's start!
Idols who say lines like this Shiritori
Ruff ruff ruff
What... ah... the "ruff" is attached to the "ruff"...
What do you mean?
Yo!
They've landed in Europe!
I'll stick my chestnut thorns in you!
Ragging is so much fun!
Yes, I'm done.
Ah, but this is good.
It's something.
Yes, then continue, yes, well, Saito.
Yes, I thought of a story I want to show you.
Oh! What do you mean?
It's a short video, and I want to make a short story.
I'm going to be alone, but I want to do a short story.
What? You've been making short stories?
Yes, I have.
For real?
Yes, I did.
Okay, Mr. Vegetable Garden, let's shoot.
Let's do it.
Scary!
Short story. I hate breaking news like this.
Oh, no! The baby lion at the zoo. It was so cute!
Oh, here comes the latest news.
Breaking news. The green onion stuck in his tooth has been removed.
I see. No, but...
I have a story to show you. No, this is the story I wanted to show you.
I have a story to show you. I wanted to show you.
The green onion stuck in his tooth has been removed.
How did you like it?
Well, it's got a simple structure.
But I'd go for something a little more melodramatic.
But it's okay.
You should keep doing this.
The more you do it, the better it gets.
I'll keep working on it.
Next is Yoshimura.
I was thinking of a riffraff version.
What does this mean?
When Mr. Ujihara was here the other day.
Muku-chan and a lot of other girls were into the "look at the picture and say 'ogiri'" type of thing.
So I thought...There were some kids who were into it, so I thought it would be a good idea.
I thought it would be a good idea.
I thought it would be nice if we used the photos of the riffraff activities.
I thought it would be fun and interesting to see how RAFL works.
I like it.
A word with pictures! Rough Ruff Version!
Ah! I can see the Budokan!
What do you mean?
Everyone was saying something like "Let's go to Budokan! It's not a story, but I know what Ruff Ruff is trying to achieve now.
I know it's not a story, but I know what Ralph is trying to achieve now.
But you're saying this now? He said it with such unexpectedness.
He explained it so well!
It was a great commentary!
I think this project itself is a good idea to use photos of riffraff.
I think it would be good to show that we do this kind of thing too!
Now, then, yes, Sasaki!
I like to say, "Give me time to think, let's get the buzz going! I like to say.
Oh, for you.
This isn't something I can put into practice today,
After all, when I watch shorts and such, I see clips of idols' live performances and such,
I often see idols' live performances cut out, and I get a lot of comments in that split second,
So I thought it would be interesting to cut out and post some footage of live performances, or scenes of people getting a little wild during dance practice,
I thought it would be fun to cut out and put up some footage of live performances or scenes of people doing something a bit more casual during dance practice.
No, Sasaki, that's good.
You've thought it through.
What was the title of your solo photo book that didn't sell at all?
Yugo Sasaki
Thanks for your hard work.
I'm the one waving the toilet pepper.
Next, Nagamatsu.
Yes, Nagamatsu.
Kido airaku de xxx.
It was popular for a while to say this in anger or in a cute way,
Recently, I don't see it so much anymore,
I wanted to do it with four different members,
I wanted to do it with four different members.
So it is neither cute nor convincing.
So you did it in the order of Kido Airaku?
Yes, I did.
Then let's do it.
Nagamatsu: Can I choose the members?
Okay, I'll do the four in the back.
Oh!
Kiyoshi!
The order will be joy, anger, sorrow, and pleasure.
The subject is...
Which is what?
But shouldn't one of the members say the subject?
I just got it.
Natsume...
What's "do"?
What?
Don't you know what it is?
What do you mean, "joy, anger, sorrow, anger"?
What shall we do? What shall we do?
What are we going to do?
I don't know what to do, I don't know what to do.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know, it's decided.
It's decided, what shall we do, love?
Love
Love.
What about pleasure?
Let's make it easy.
It's decided. What shall we do? Love.
No, it's not.
That's all I want to explain.
Positivity, anger, sorrow, emotion...
So you have to get angry.
Angry, yes.
Okay.
Anger, sorrow, joy, anger, anger, sorrow, emotion, Arinchi.
Affricate
Do
Yurichi!
Yriety!
Yuri-chi!
Oh, that's good!
No, but it's good. Everyone seems to work well together.
Surprisingly, I'm not sure if I like Sasaki's...
Yurichii!
I liked it a lot.
It's fun to be out of the loop.
I'm glad, I'm glad.
It's good.
Okay, let's continue with Himi's.
Yes, HIMINO. There's a ramen noodle lover JD's ramen by herself.
Oh!
This is a story about how I like ramen and how I always feel when I go alone.
I thought it wouldn't be like a riffraff if I did it in a normal way, so I thought I'd just do it as an aru aru.
May I show you something?
Aru Aru Ramen Aru Aru by myself?
Here we go.
Ramen noodle lover JD's one-man ramen experience
Oh, thank you for the hair!
Oh, no, I have my own stuff.
I'm going to get water by myself.
Oh, I'm sorry, thank you.
Auntie waitresses tend to take care of you because you're a girl
It was a pattern of contrast, wasn't it?
I see... I see.I see. I see.
I see. I see.
So you're saying that you're going to do what you think is a certain thing, one at a time.
Indeed.
But that's okay.
No one else is doing it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm just doing a certain thing about my hobbies.
Okay, then, let's continue.
Okay, okay, then, Furitaki.
I was like, "Oh my God, right before today...
You said I had to be able to do something.
I had to rethink a lot.
It's so boring.
What?
I'm sorry. It's called the VS Anime Quiz.
I'm an anime fan.
I don't care if you're a member or not.
But if it's a quiz, people who watch the show take the quiz.
So the number of comments increases a lot.
Like, "I could do this," or "I couldn't do this, but I could answer all the others.
or "I couldn't do this one, but I could answer all the others.
So it's like a challenge for everyone.
Yes.
But if it's an easy one, I can do it.
But first of all, this group doesn't watch anime.
It's okay if they don't.
Oh, well, I see.
So, in that case...
Have dinner with us.
Anime quiz!
Now, the first question!
Which pillar character appeared in the Blade of Demons: Infinity Train Arc?
Zenkoku-san
Correct answer.
Wait!
This is not a home video.
Correct! It's not.
Let's put someone who doesn't know anime on the phone for you.
Arisa.
I don't watch it at all.
Not at all?
Not at all.
Anime Quiz Question #2
Give the full name of the son of your favorite child's love.
I see.
Full name?
I showed you.
I said I saw it.
I only watched about 40 minutes.
That's right.
Hayato Sasaki.
Yes!
It looks like something out of Yu-Gi-Oh!
Well, it's true, though, isn't it?
It's a carrot-shaped thing.
It would be interesting if we could do something with it.
But Fujisaki's problem is surprisingly good.
It's good.
Just right.
Good job.
Next, Hayashi.
Okay, uh, JK quarrel audition.
What's this?
You want to get into an argument?
Yes, you were arguing with a gal.
Then why don't you get into an argument with JK?
Oh, I'm going to get into an argument with you?
I don't want to.
You and Mr. Sakama in the woods?
Let's have a quarrel.
Hey, hey, hey!
No, I don't want to.
I don't want to.
Let's go.
Next in line, please.
What is it?
I don't know what you want. You're a little guy, aren't you?
Huh. I don't know. Tiny ones are cuter.
Huh?
No, it's not cute when you're big.
It was a long time ago that tiny girls were cuter.
It still is.
Wait a minute.
More, more, faster.
If you're going to do it, you have to put more in.
You have to put more in.
You have to go so fast that you can't cut it.
Even now. Even now.
Okay, next.
I think I hear a sniffle coming from you.
You used to be a backstage worker, didn't you?
I was behind the scenes, but I've been accumulating one by one to get to the front.
I wonder if you can be in the front.
You did your best.
I did my best.
You work hard, too.
I'll do my best.I'll do my best.
No, no, no, no, no. I'll do my best, sweetie. No, no, no, no, no.
It's you.
You said I can't lose, Hayashi.
You said you could do it.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Don't tell me it was fun.
It's not about making memories.
It's like, "I can do something else.
I hear you want to do it.
I want to do it.
I want to do an audition for an argument.
FujisakiI'm scared.
He can make faces.
I'm scared.
A little prick came in.
What? Do you lick average height?
There's nothing to lick about average height.
What's there to lick about average height?
It's normal. What do you mean, "shorty"?
Well, if you look tiny, then maybe you don't have aura.
I have a tiny face.
Maybe it's the face that's tiny,
I mean, he looked a little tiny,
You admit it.
Maybe I didn't feel the aura.
Can we stop? This.
I mean, really, look at you,
I'm not sure what I'm going to do with this riffraff.
I mean, why do I have to badmouth this guy and the girl I produce?
I mean, why do I have to say bad things about this guy and this girl I'm producing?
I have to say, "What a dick.
But Fujisaki is still strong.
Stronger than Hayashi.
Natsume wants to do it too.
Natsume's last one. Natsume wants to do it too.
I don't like it.
Hey, a title.
Is this it?
Yeah.
It's a match between Natsume and Title.
What's this?
Okay, next one, please.
Shut up.
May I? Your face is disgusting.
I said it in a low voice.
You've got the wrong guy.
I can't hear you.
What?
Hmm?
Can you move where you're sitting?
Why?
You're on the listening side.
The listener's over here.
What? What?
I can't hear you.
Can't you speak up?
I'm talking fine.
I'll listen if you tell me.
I'm sorry.
Don't listen to him.
I was going to tell you.
It's too obvious.
It's too ordinary.
There's nothing to see.
There's no words, no words.
I've never said a bad word before.
It's hard.
I'm sorry, I didn't know how to say it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know... I've come up with a lot of stuff, but...
I don't know.
So, are you going to be able to upload the pictures that you took today?
In terms of atmosphere...
Some of the stuff I took today was kind of fun.
Let's go back and look at them again later.
Let's see if we can get some of them up.
Let's do that.
Let's do some more after this video is up.
after this video is uploaded.
Yes, I'll do that.
Well, in the future...
If there's anything we can do in the future...
I'd like to do it.
I'll update this page as needed.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Thank you for watching until the end.
What did you think of today's episode?
Hey, did you enjoy it? What did you like?
Tell me the truth.
I'm not mad at you. Just tell me the truth.
I'm not mad at you.
Yeah, I'm not mad.
You can tell me what you thought in the comments section or on Twitter.
Please, just tell me what you think.
I'm begging you.